mybtfile.com 2016-12-02

# Mybtfile.com - Free File Hosting

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Mybtfiles.com 

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**  
This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Mybtfiles.com. If there are any exceptions, Mybtfiles.com will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information. Mybtfiles.com provides links to web sites operated by third parties, and also provides search results and similar Services to third parties for display on their own web sites or applications. Mybtfiles.com is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party web sites or applications. 

**Online Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

**What information does Mybtfiles.com collect and how is it used?**  
Mybtfiles.com may collect any or all of the following three types of information: (a) traffic or click-through data, (b) cookies, or (c) contact information and other personally identifying information. Mybtfiles.com’s collection and use of each type of data is described below, as well as the ways (if any) in which the data may be shared with third parties. 

(a) Traffic or Click-Through Data. Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. Mybtfiles.com may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our web site. Mybtfiles.com collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) users access. For example, Mybtfiles.com ‘s servers collect information about the site from which you entered to enable Mybtfiles.com to calculate and pay its affiliates, information about the most frequently searched terms to help its advertisers provide the most relevant search results, information about usage to check for fraudulent behavior. (b) Cookies. Mybtfiles.com collects information about online behavior using cookies. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning. Mybtfiles.com cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies lets us know about repeat visitors, Mybtfiles.com may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of Mybtfiles.com. Mybtfiles.com may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. (c) Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information. Mybtfiles.com can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become an affiliate with Mybtfiles.com, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from Mybtfiles.com and provide your name or return contact information, or when you register for the advanced features of Mybtfiles.com. 

Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or click-through data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request. During the registration process, you may be asked to provide certain information, including contact information and other personally identifying information. Mybtfiles.com will use registration information to provide updates, and other business purposes related to making available the features and functions of Mybtfiles.com. Mybtfiles.com may use registration information to make users aware of new products or special offers or promotions. Mybtfiles.com will abide by requests from you (in accordance with the procedure below) to discontinue such use. Mybtfiles.com stores personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely (as described below) and considers it part of the assets of its business. Mybtfiles.com may provide certain registration information to third parties for use in marketing and in designing or providing their own services. 

**Is data stored by Mybtfiles.com secure?**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Mybtfiles.com has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Mybtfiles.com (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Mybtfiles.com will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

**Does Mybtfiles.com collect personally identifying information from or about children?**  
Mybtfiles.com uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 18. The Services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any portions of the Services that require registration. 

**How can I access or correct any personally identifying information about me?**  
To request a copy of the personally identifiable information you have sent to Mybtfiles.com, please send an e-mail containing your request to online.media.inc@gmail.com. You must provide your full name and the e-mail from which the request is received (and to which the response will be sent) must match the e-mail on file with Mybtfiles.com. You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the e-mail. 

**How do I find out more about Mybtfiles.com’s information practices?**  
If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact us via email, and someone will get back to you ASAP. 

You may also use the above contact information if you think any information about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or if you want to change the sort of information about you that Mybtfiles.com may have collected. Please bookmark this page and check back frequently because we do make frequent updates to this privacy policy. 

Note: we do not allow any illegal file upload to our site.  
You can use this hosting service only if you agree to and accept the Terms of Use. 

* * *

Contact | Privacy Policy | Terms of Use

© 2014 Mybtfiles.com. All rights reserved.
